{
  "activeEventId" : false,
  "admins" : {
    "0s3r7yEj7gRzNoFaW2wGfzwWyub2" : true,
    "5biIuUJKBDV6dOVvRzSoXpDyEaN2" : true,
    "5j6igMzdffTqGY3BuunaKPWVVQN2" : true,
    "HrnFh8lr76UEBtR2d32cBXBqFx33" : true,
    "aK6xWtxovRTz0gaAjIlFgn6dhgo1" : true,
    "cjDL28OF3AN4qnyq6p4yZt2HOpB3" : true,
    "h1eWfB0CfTTcr7XKnqyav8ceHgq2" : true,
    "lNcu9GkIvuZmoo31l9gdoFjvRAj2" : true,
    "sAysvz3egIMLFpQAQlulRsP1eW72" : true
  },
  "disableAll" : false,
  "events" : {
    "-LCUbqaXAuNRGFOJBXEL" : {
      "activeGameId" : false,
      "alias" : "beer30",
      "gameWaitBeforeQuestionsCopy" : {
        "description" : "Answer all six questions (no stopping for wrong answers) as fast as you can. 10 seconds per question. Speed and accuracy win. Here comes the first question.",
        "title" : "Let's Play!"
      },
      "games" : {
        "-LDqh9b_wCchDyU_C1Fj" : true,
        "-LDqiG2CZKRF37yudI4t" : true,
        "-LDqjcYxEOv7InRdlXem" : true,
        "-LDqkjkaEtSZ6CvpXEEk" : true,
        "-LDqnMbKKeZxU_ulHyPc" : true,
        "-LDqxAKR82FLwX4sB_PE" : true
      },
      "hashtag" : "#DEGBEER30",
      "leaderboardCopy" : {
        "description" : "Congrats on seeing your name in lights. Don't let someone steal your thunder. Play again to maintain your spot."
      },
      "name" : "DEG Beer:30",
      "postgameResultsCopy" : {
        "description" : "Thanks for playing! See you again next week."
      },
      "pregameRotatingCopy" : {
        "-LDrOVz5N4PlxTiRRg4_" : "This prize isn’t going to win itself. ",
        "-LDrOXqv8GbBfTNbojz3" : "Tip: Play as many games as you can. Scores are accumulated. Plus, we like you. ",
        "-LDrOZCILfoMJHAgeRBZ" : "You’ve gotta ask yourself one question: “Do I feel lucky?”",
        "-LDrO_WBpXRnWO4Cuny3" : "Tip: Try not to use all 10 seconds answering a question. Speed matters.",
        "-LDrOb-udJuTjbd6D2dx" : "Win or lose, at least we'll have shared this moment together.",
        "-LDrOctx12XGHvAspYac" : "Warm up those thumbs and get ready to win some prizes. ",
        "-LDrOeIiZDpMZcgxe82T" : "Your high school teachers are about to either be very proud or very disappointed.",
        "-LDrOfjD29eAMSHKgd4f" : "Tip: Answer every question, even if you get one wrong. We’re all about forgiveness.",
        "-LDrOh5qJ60f9j1gZre0" : "No pressure, no diamonds.",
        "-LDrOjHSlTHoQp2tRYrD" : "There are no participation ribbons in trivia."
      },
      "registrationCopy" : {
        "disclosure" : "By filling out this form, you are opting in to receiving notifications regarding DEG Trivia via email and SMS, as well as general follow-up communications from the agency. Learn more about <a href=\"https://www.degdigital.com/deg-full-service-digital-agency/privacy-policy/\" target=\"_blank\">DEG’s privacy policy</a>.",
        "title" : "Welcome to DEG Trivia!"
      },
      "tvCopy" : {
        "url" : "degtrivia.com"
      }
    },
    "-LD84ESzyLp4oyyDckO2" : {
      "activeGameId" : false,
      "alias" : "cnxtrivia2018",
      "gameWaitBeforeQuestionsCopy" : {
        "description" : "Answer all six questions (no stopping for wrong answers) as fast as you can. 10 seconds per question. Speed and accuracy win. Here comes the first question.",
        "title" : "Let's Play!"
      },
      "games" : {
        "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHlU" : true,
        "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4Yp" : true,
        "-LD8IC8J0BOq2zjs_GmY" : true,
        "-LD8JGHNeTmMiRFuyhzW" : true,
        "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQSH" : true,
        "-LD8MSLGcb5uw-GhlJlp" : true
      },
      "hashtag" : "#CNXTRIVIA",
      "leaderboardCopy" : {
        "description" : "Thanks for playing Connections Trivia. If you see your name in lights, congrats! If you don’t, remember, it’s all about having fun anyway."
      },
      "name" : "CNX 2018",
      "postgameResultsCopy" : {
        "description" : "Eager for more knowledge? Stop by booth #303 to learn how to make the most of your marketing program."
      },
      "pregameRotatingCopy" : {
        "-LDrNuHhq0tUD7TWilzW" : "Tip: Stop by DEG’s booth #303 while you wait. You never know when an answer could be hiding in plain sight.",
        "-LDrO-JvIbdoE377ZJPr" : "This prize isn’t going to win itself.",
        "-LDrO1RsFIJGm8SsaWxb" : "Tip: Play as many games as you can. Scores are accumulated. Plus, we like you.",
        "-LDrO3Lxt0Q9KgElg7iX" : "You’ve gotta ask yourself one question: “Do I feel lucky?”",
        "-LDrO4YkyXn3r4T8t7EJ" : "Tip: Try not to use all 10 seconds answering a question. Speed matters. ",
        "-LDrO73iedMz3jMNATia" : "Win or lose, at least we'll have shared this moment together.",
        "-LDrO9kjeGnJ3npSv0OR" : "Warm up those thumbs and get ready to win some prizes.",
        "-LDrOBQ2uvwl0Tp7xPbI" : "Your high school teachers are about to either be very proud or very disappointed.",
        "-LDrODM6s4dLH_XnzlS7" : "Tip: Answer every question, even if you get one wrong. We’re all about forgiveness.",
        "-LDrOEyNEtZqLWcnXsfn" : "No pressure, no diamonds.",
        "-LDrOGfpKFatEDdhPR4E" : "Tip: Do you know what city you’re in? That’s a good start.",
        "-LDrOI_JMZ0BiVMNrpES" : "There are no participation ribbons in trivia."
      },
      "registrationCopy" : {
        "disclosure" : "By filling out this form, you are opting in to receiving notifications regarding Connections trivia via email and SMS, as well as general follow-up communications from the agency. Learn more about <a href=\"https://www.degdigital.com/deg-full-service-digital-agency/privacy-policy/\" target=\"_blank\">DEG’s privacy policy</a>.",
        "title" : "Welcome to Connections Trivia, presented by DEG."
      },
      "tvCopy" : {
        "message1" : "DEG is a full service marketing agency here to help you.",
        "message2" : "Let us help you market to the moment."
      },
      "url" : "cnxtrivia.com"
    }
  },
  "games" : {
    "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHlU" : {
      "activeQuestionId" : false,
      "event" : "-LD84ESzyLp4oyyDckO2",
      "name" : "Game 1",
      "questionExpirationTime" : 1527644974024,
      "questions" : {
        "-LD8FrG-yF6EXlmDHn4_" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHl1" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Westworld"
            },
            "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHl2" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Games of Thrones"
            },
            "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHl3" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Mickey Mouse Club"
            },
            "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHl4" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "The Walking Dead"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHl2",
          "order" : 0,
          "question" : "Which HBO show was the most watched TV series of 2017?"
        },
        "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHl5" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHl6" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Newton"
            },
            "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHl7" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Trailhead"
            },
            "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHl8" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Carl"
            },
            "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHl9" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Einstein"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHl9",
          "order" : 1,
          "question" : "What is the name of Salesforce's AI technology?"
        },
        "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHlA" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHlB" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Chance the Rapper"
            },
            "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHlC" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Jay-Z"
            },
            "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHlD" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Kanye West"
            },
            "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHlE" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Ice Cube"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHlD",
          "order" : 2,
          "question" : "Which Chicago-born rapper named his daughter after his hometown?"
        },
        "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHlF" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHlG" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Justin Timberlake"
            },
            "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHlH" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Katy Perry"
            },
            "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHlI" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Lady Gaga"
            },
            "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHlJ" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Beyoncé "
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHlG",
          "order" : 3,
          "question" : "Who performed during halftime of the 2018 Super Bowl?"
        },
        "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHlK" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHlL" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Robin Williams"
            },
            "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHlM" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Larry Bird"
            },
            "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHlN" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Russell Crowe"
            },
            "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHlO" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHlM",
          "order" : 4,
          "question" : "Twitter's icon is named after whom?"
        },
        "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHlP" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHlQ" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "5 years"
            },
            "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHlR" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "14 years"
            },
            "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHlS" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "100 years"
            },
            "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHlT" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "9 years"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8FrG0NCS0bNPLXHlR",
          "order" : 5,
          "question" : "How long has DEG been a Salesforce partner?"
        }
      },
      "showGameOver" : false,
      "showGameResults" : false,
      "showQuestionResults" : false,
      "startTime" : 1528822800000
    },
    "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4Yp" : {
      "activeQuestionId" : false,
      "event" : "-LD84ESzyLp4oyyDckO2",
      "name" : "Game 2",
      "questions" : {
        "-LD8Gu0MZM4y9_sBkh28" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8Gu0MZM4y9_sBkh29" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Darth Vader"
            },
            "-LD8Gu0NR2NXEakLikMx" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Han Solo"
            },
            "-LD8Gu0NR2NXEakLikMy" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Chewbacca"
            },
            "-LD8Gu0NR2NXEakLikMz" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "C3PO"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8Gu0NR2NXEakLikMx",
          "order" : 0,
          "question" : "The latest movie in the Star Wars universe, released on May 25, focuses on which character?"
        },
        "-LD8Gu0NR2NXEakLikN-" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4YS" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Erie"
            },
            "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4YT" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Superior"
            },
            "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4YU" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Huron"
            },
            "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4YV" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Michigan"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4YV",
          "order" : 1,
          "question" : "Chicago rests on the edge of what Great Lake?"
        },
        "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4YW" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4YX" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "2004"
            },
            "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4YY" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "2005"
            },
            "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4YZ" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "2001"
            },
            "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4Y_" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "2007"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4YX",
          "order" : 2,
          "question" : "What year was Facebook founded?"
        },
        "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4Ya" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4Yb" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Cinnamon"
            },
            "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4Yc" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Honey"
            },
            "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4Yd" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Molasses"
            },
            "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4Ye" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Maple syrup"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4Yd",
          "order" : 3,
          "question" : "What ingredient is added to white sugar to make brown sugar?"
        },
        "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4Yf" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4Yg" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "38"
            },
            "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4Yh" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "131"
            },
            "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4Yi" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "72"
            },
            "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4Yj" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "300"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4Yh",
          "order" : 4,
          "question" : "On average, how many business emails are sent and received per day per person?"
        },
        "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4Yk" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4Yl" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Nikon"
            },
            "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4Ym" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "AMC Theatres"
            },
            "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4Yn" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "PacSun"
            },
            "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4Yo" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "All of the above"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8Gu0OMUVi02Ixl4Yo",
          "order" : 5,
          "question" : "Which brand is a DEG client?"
        }
      },
      "showGameOver" : false,
      "showGameResults" : false,
      "showQuestionResults" : false,
      "startTime" : 1528830000000
    },
    "-LD8IC8J0BOq2zjs_GmY" : {
      "activeQuestionId" : false,
      "event" : "-LD84ESzyLp4oyyDckO2",
      "name" : "Game 3",
      "questions" : {
        "-LD8IC8HgxfGy266VMPM" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8IC8HgxfGy266VMPN" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Go For It"
            },
            "-LD8IC8HgxfGy266VMPO" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Just Do It"
            },
            "-LD8IC8HgxfGy266VMPP" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "You Can Do It"
            },
            "-LD8IC8HgxfGy266VMPQ" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Make It Happen"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8IC8HgxfGy266VMPO",
          "order" : 0,
          "question" : "What is Nike's famous slogan?"
        },
        "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9A" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9B" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "2001"
            },
            "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9C" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "1776"
            },
            "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9D" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "1999"
            },
            "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9E" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "1984"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9E",
          "order" : 1,
          "question" : "What year is also the title of the dystopian George Orwell novel about the always-watching Big Brother? "
        },
        "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9F" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9G" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Ultimate Support Bank"
            },
            "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9H" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Universal Serial Bus"
            },
            "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9I" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Universal Software Bank"
            },
            "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9J" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Unix Support Bus"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9H",
          "order" : 2,
          "question" : "What does the acronym USB stand for when referring to a computer port?"
        },
        "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9K" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9L" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "6"
            },
            "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9M" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "4"
            },
            "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9N" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "3"
            },
            "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9O" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "5"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9L",
          "order" : 3,
          "question" : "The United States is spread out across how many time zones?"
        },
        "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9P" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9Q" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Ajay Bhatt"
            },
            "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9R" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Ray Tomlinson"
            },
            "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9S" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Paul Buchheit"
            },
            "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9T" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Ray Bradbury"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9R",
          "order" : 4,
          "question" : "Who is credited with sending the first email?"
        },
        "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9U" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9V" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "A full-service digital agency"
            },
            "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9W" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "A platinum Salesforce partner"
            },
            "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9X" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "A cross-cloud Salesforce implementation specialist"
            },
            "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9Y" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "All of the above"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8IC8IgIeTajeoNg9Y",
          "order" : 5,
          "question" : "What is DEG?"
        }
      },
      "showGameOver" : false,
      "showGameResults" : false,
      "showQuestionResults" : false,
      "startTime" : 1528837200000
    },
    "-LD8JGHNeTmMiRFuyhzW" : {
      "activeQuestionId" : false,
      "event" : "-LD84ESzyLp4oyyDckO2",
      "name" : "Game 4",
      "questions" : {
        "-LD8JGHLDgxI5Taxcu7a" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8JGHM-RWJ4O7uPB1u" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Clothes"
            },
            "-LD8JGHM-RWJ4O7uPB1v" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "CDs"
            },
            "-LD8JGHM-RWJ4O7uPB1w" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Books"
            },
            "-LD8JGHM-RWJ4O7uPB1x" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Safari vacations"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8JGHM-RWJ4O7uPB1w",
          "order" : 0,
          "question" : "What was the first type of product sold on Amazon?"
        },
        "-LD8JGHM-RWJ4O7uPB1y" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8JGHM-RWJ4O7uPB1z" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "England"
            },
            "-LD8JGHM-RWJ4O7uPB2-" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "France"
            },
            "-LD8JGHM-RWJ4O7uPB20" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Brazil"
            },
            "-LD8JGHM-RWJ4O7uPB21" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Russia"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8JGHM-RWJ4O7uPB21",
          "order" : 1,
          "question" : "The 2018 World Cup is taking place in what country?"
        },
        "-LD8JGHM-RWJ4O7uPB22" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8JGHM-RWJ4O7uPB23" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "4.2 billion"
            },
            "-LD8JGHM-RWJ4O7uPB24" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "1.8 billion"
            },
            "-LD8JGHM-RWJ4O7uPB25" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "6.1 billion"
            },
            "-LD8JGHM-RWJ4O7uPB26" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "7.5 billion"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8JGHM-RWJ4O7uPB23",
          "order" : 2,
          "question" : "Out of the 7.6 billion people in the world, how many are Internet users?"
        },
        "-LD8JGHM-RWJ4O7uPB27" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8JGHM-RWJ4O7uPB28" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Wired"
            },
            "-LD8JGHM-RWJ4O7uPB29" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "The Internet Movie Database"
            },
            "-LD8JGHM-RWJ4O7uPB2A" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "MTV"
            },
            "-LD8JGHM-RWJ4O7uPB2B" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "America Online"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8JGHM-RWJ4O7uPB28",
          "order" : 3,
          "question" : "Which company created the first web banner ad?"
        },
        "-LD8JGHM-RWJ4O7uPB2C" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8JGHM-RWJ4O7uPB2D" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "The Bible"
            },
            "-LD8JGHM-RWJ4O7uPB2E" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Guinness Book of World Records"
            },
            "-LD8JGHM-RWJ4O7uPB2F" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "A Tale of Two Cities"
            },
            "-LD8JGHM-RWJ4O7uPB2G" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Twilight"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8JGHM-RWJ4O7uPB2E",
          "order" : 4,
          "question" : "Which book holds the record of being the most stolen book from public libraries?"
        },
        "-LD8JGHNeTmMiRFuyhzR" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8JGHNeTmMiRFuyhzS" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "0"
            },
            "-LD8JGHNeTmMiRFuyhzT" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "3"
            },
            "-LD8JGHNeTmMiRFuyhzU" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "1"
            },
            "-LD8JGHNeTmMiRFuyhzV" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "2"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8JGHNeTmMiRFuyhzT",
          "order" : 5,
          "question" : "DEG is the only Salesforce partner to be named Marketing Cloud Partner of the Year how many times?"
        }
      },
      "showGameOver" : false,
      "showGameResults" : false,
      "showQuestionResults" : false,
      "startTime" : 1528844400000
    },
    "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQSH" : {
      "activeQuestionId" : false,
      "event" : "-LD84ESzyLp4oyyDckO2",
      "name" : "Game 5",
      "questions" : {
        "-LD8KdB7HtuzfuNJZXPb" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQRp" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Louvre"
            },
            "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQRq" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Van Gough"
            },
            "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQRr" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Rijksmuseum"
            },
            "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQRs" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "British Museum"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQRp",
          "order" : 0,
          "question" : "What is the most visited museum in Europe?"
        },
        "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQRt" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQRu" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "96 years"
            },
            "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQRv" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "48 years"
            },
            "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQRw" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "108 years"
            },
            "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQRx" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "59 years"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQRw",
          "order" : 1,
          "question" : "Before winning the World Series in 2016, how many years did the Chicago Cubs go between winning a title?"
        },
        "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQRy" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQRz" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Moby Dick"
            },
            "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQS-" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "The Old Man and the Sea"
            },
            "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQS0" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Typee"
            },
            "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQS1" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "20,000 Leagues Under the Sea"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQRz",
          "order" : 2,
          "question" : "The name Starbucks was inspired by the first mate in what Herman Melville novel?"
        },
        "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQS2" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQS3" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "The X-Files"
            },
            "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQS4" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Saturday Night Live"
            },
            "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQS5" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Mystery Science Theater 3000"
            },
            "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQS6" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Monty Python"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQS6",
          "order" : 3,
          "question" : "The term 'spam' was first used to refer to junk messages on what TV show?"
        },
        "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQS7" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQS8" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Charles Darwin"
            },
            "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQS9" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Oliver Cromwell"
            },
            "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQSA" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Winston Churchill"
            },
            "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQSB" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Sir Isaac Newton"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQSA",
          "order" : 4,
          "question" : "The late Diana, Princess of Wales, was distantly related to which prominent historical figure?"
        },
        "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQSC" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQSD" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Kansas City"
            },
            "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQSE" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Denver"
            },
            "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQSF" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "San Francisco"
            },
            "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQSG" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "New York"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8KdB8YCBVcXHGpQSD",
          "order" : 5,
          "question" : "Where is DEG headquartered?"
        }
      },
      "showGameOver" : false,
      "showGameResults" : false,
      "showQuestionResults" : false,
      "startTime" : 1528851600000
    },
    "-LD8MSLGcb5uw-GhlJlp" : {
      "activeQuestionId" : false,
      "event" : "-LD84ESzyLp4oyyDckO2",
      "name" : "Game 6",
      "questions" : {
        "-LD8MSLFyQsWQmfECQ6e" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8MSLFyQsWQmfECQ6f" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "&"
            },
            "-LD8MSLFyQsWQmfECQ6g" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "@"
            },
            "-LD8MSLFyQsWQmfECQ6h" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "%"
            },
            "-LD8MSLFyQsWQmfECQ6i" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "#"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8MSLFyQsWQmfECQ6g",
          "order" : 0,
          "question" : "What symbol is used in an email address to indicate where the message is intended to go?"
        },
        "-LD8MSLFyQsWQmfECQ6j" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8MSLFyQsWQmfECQ6k" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "6"
            },
            "-LD8MSLFyQsWQmfECQ6l" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "5"
            },
            "-LD8MSLFyQsWQmfECQ6m" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "7"
            },
            "-LD8MSLFyQsWQmfECQ6n" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "4"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8MSLFyQsWQmfECQ6m",
          "order" : 1,
          "question" : "How many red stripes are on the United States flag?"
        },
        "-LD8MSLFyQsWQmfECQ6o" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8MSLFyQsWQmfECQ6p" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "WebCrawl"
            },
            "-LD8MSLFyQsWQmfECQ6q" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Backrub"
            },
            "-LD8MSLFyQsWQmfECQ6r" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Handshake"
            },
            "-LD8MSLFyQsWQmfECQ6s" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Hopscotch"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8MSLFyQsWQmfECQ6q",
          "order" : 2,
          "question" : "What was the original name of the search engine now known as Google?"
        },
        "-LD8MSLGcb5uw-GhlJla" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8MSLGcb5uw-GhlJlb" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Oprah"
            },
            "-LD8MSLGcb5uw-GhlJlc" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Martha Stewart"
            },
            "-LD8MSLGcb5uw-GhlJld" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Guy Fieri"
            },
            "-LD8MSLGcb5uw-GhlJle" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Ina Garten"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8MSLGcb5uw-GhlJlc",
          "order" : 3,
          "question" : "In 2016, Snoop Dogg co-starred alongside which lifestyle guru on their collaborative cooking show 'Potluck Dinner Party'?"
        },
        "-LD8MSLGcb5uw-GhlJlf" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8MSLGcb5uw-GhlJlg" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Marketing Cloud"
            },
            "-LD8MSLGcb5uw-GhlJlh" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Commerce Cloud"
            },
            "-LD8MSLGcb5uw-GhlJli" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Service Cloud"
            },
            "-LD8MSLGcb5uw-GhlJlj" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Journey Cloud"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8MSLGcb5uw-GhlJlj",
          "order" : 4,
          "question" : "Which of these is not one of Salesforce's Clouds?"
        },
        "-LD8MSLGcb5uw-GhlJlk" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LD8MSLGcb5uw-GhlJll" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Customers"
            },
            "-LD8MSLGcb5uw-GhlJlm" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Environments"
            },
            "-LD8MSLGcb5uw-GhlJln" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Moments"
            },
            "-LD8MSLGcb5uw-GhlJlo" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Brands"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LD8MSLGcb5uw-GhlJln",
          "order" : 5,
          "question" : "In DEG's tagline, the agency proclaims that it markets to what?"
        }
      },
      "showGameOver" : false,
      "showGameResults" : false,
      "showQuestionResults" : false,
      "startTime" : 1528858800000
    },
    "-LDqh9b_wCchDyU_C1Fj" : {
      "activeQuestionId" : false,
      "event" : "-LCUbqaXAuNRGFOJBXEL",
      "name" : "06/01/18 Game 1",
      "questions" : {
        "-LDqh9bYUx_8g4vk9VLP" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqh9bYUx_8g4vk9VLQ" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Westworld"
            },
            "-LDqh9bYUx_8g4vk9VLR" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Games of Thrones"
            },
            "-LDqh9bZbnMrGPkrj7CP" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Mickey Mouse Club"
            },
            "-LDqh9bZbnMrGPkrj7CQ" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "The Walking Dead"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqh9bYUx_8g4vk9VLR",
          "order" : 0,
          "question" : "Which HBO show was the most watched TV series of 2017?"
        },
        "-LDqh9bZbnMrGPkrj7CR" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqh9bZbnMrGPkrj7CS" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Newton"
            },
            "-LDqh9bZbnMrGPkrj7CT" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Trailhead"
            },
            "-LDqh9bZbnMrGPkrj7CU" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Carl"
            },
            "-LDqh9bZbnMrGPkrj7CV" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Einstein"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqh9bZbnMrGPkrj7CV",
          "order" : 1,
          "question" : "What is the name of Salesforce's AI technology?"
        },
        "-LDqh9bZbnMrGPkrj7CW" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqh9bZbnMrGPkrj7CX" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Chance the Rapper"
            },
            "-LDqh9bZbnMrGPkrj7CY" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Jay-Z"
            },
            "-LDqh9b_wCchDyU_C1FT" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Kanye West"
            },
            "-LDqh9b_wCchDyU_C1FU" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Ice Cube"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqh9b_wCchDyU_C1FT",
          "order" : 2,
          "question" : "Which Chicago-born rapper named his daughter after his hometown?"
        },
        "-LDqh9b_wCchDyU_C1FV" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqh9b_wCchDyU_C1FW" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Justin Timberlake"
            },
            "-LDqh9b_wCchDyU_C1FX" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Katy Perry"
            },
            "-LDqh9b_wCchDyU_C1FY" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Lady Gaga"
            },
            "-LDqh9b_wCchDyU_C1FZ" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Beyoncé"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqh9b_wCchDyU_C1FW",
          "order" : 3,
          "question" : "Who performed during halftime of the 2018 Super Bowl?"
        },
        "-LDqh9b_wCchDyU_C1F_" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqh9b_wCchDyU_C1Fa" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Robin Williams"
            },
            "-LDqh9b_wCchDyU_C1Fb" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Larry Bird"
            },
            "-LDqh9b_wCchDyU_C1Fc" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Russell Crowe"
            },
            "-LDqh9b_wCchDyU_C1Fd" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqh9b_wCchDyU_C1Fb",
          "order" : 4,
          "question" : "Twitter's icon is named after whom?"
        },
        "-LDqh9b_wCchDyU_C1Fe" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqh9b_wCchDyU_C1Ff" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "5 years"
            },
            "-LDqh9b_wCchDyU_C1Fg" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "14 years"
            },
            "-LDqh9b_wCchDyU_C1Fh" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "100 years"
            },
            "-LDqh9b_wCchDyU_C1Fi" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "9 years"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqh9b_wCchDyU_C1Fg",
          "order" : 5,
          "question" : "How long has DEG been a Salesforce partner?"
        }
      },
      "showGameOver" : false,
      "showGameResults" : false,
      "showQuestionResults" : false,
      "startTime" : 1527888600000
    },
    "-LDqiG2CZKRF37yudI4t" : {
      "activeQuestionId" : false,
      "event" : "-LCUbqaXAuNRGFOJBXEL",
      "name" : "06/01/18 Game 2",
      "questions" : {
        "-LDqiG2AHnE1RgG5mo_Y" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqiG2AHnE1RgG5mo_Z" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Darth Vader"
            },
            "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuEl" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Han Solo"
            },
            "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuEm" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Chewbacca"
            },
            "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuEn" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "C3PO"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuEl",
          "order" : 0,
          "question" : "The latest movie in the Star Wars universe, released on May 25, focuses on which character?"
        },
        "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuEo" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuEp" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Erie"
            },
            "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuEq" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Superior"
            },
            "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuEr" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Huron"
            },
            "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuEs" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Michigan"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuEs",
          "order" : 1,
          "question" : "Chicago rests on the edge of what Great Lake?"
        },
        "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuEt" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuEu" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "2004"
            },
            "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuEv" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "2005"
            },
            "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuEw" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "2001"
            },
            "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuEx" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "2007"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuEu",
          "order" : 2,
          "question" : "What year was Facebook founded?"
        },
        "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuEy" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuEz" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Cinnamon"
            },
            "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuF-" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Honey"
            },
            "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuF0" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Molasses"
            },
            "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuF1" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Maple syrup"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuF0",
          "order" : 3,
          "question" : "What ingredient is added to white sugar to make brown sugar?"
        },
        "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuF2" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuF3" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "38"
            },
            "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuF4" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "131"
            },
            "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuF5" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "72"
            },
            "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuF6" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "300"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuF4",
          "order" : 4,
          "question" : "On average, how many business emails are sent and received per day per person?"
        },
        "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuF7" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuF8" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Nikon"
            },
            "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuF9" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "AMC Theatres"
            },
            "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuFA" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "PacSun"
            },
            "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuFB" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "All of the above"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqiG2BM3LJeZYqvuFB",
          "order" : 5,
          "question" : "Which brand is a DEG client?"
        }
      },
      "showGameOver" : false,
      "showGameResults" : false,
      "showQuestionResults" : false,
      "startTime" : 1527889200000
    },
    "-LDqjcYxEOv7InRdlXem" : {
      "activeQuestionId" : false,
      "event" : "-LCUbqaXAuNRGFOJBXEL",
      "name" : "06/01/18 Game 3",
      "questions" : {
        "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1_c" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1_d" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Go For It"
            },
            "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1_e" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Just Do It"
            },
            "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1_f" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "You Can Do It"
            },
            "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1_g" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Make It Happen"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1_f",
          "order" : 0,
          "question" : "What is Nike's famous slogan?"
        },
        "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1_h" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1_i" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "2001"
            },
            "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1_j" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "1776"
            },
            "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1_k" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "1999"
            },
            "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1_l" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "1984"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1_l",
          "order" : 1,
          "question" : "What year is also the title of the dystopian George Orwell novel about the always-watching Big Brother?"
        },
        "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1_m" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1_n" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Ultimate Support Bank"
            },
            "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1_o" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Universal Serial Bus"
            },
            "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1_p" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Universal Software Bank"
            },
            "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1_q" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Unix Support Bus"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1_o",
          "order" : 2,
          "question" : "What does the acronym USB stand for when referring to a computer port?"
        },
        "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1_r" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1_s" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "6"
            },
            "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1_t" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "4"
            },
            "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1_u" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "3"
            },
            "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1_v" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "5"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1_s",
          "order" : 3,
          "question" : "The United States is spread out across how many time zones?"
        },
        "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1_w" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1_x" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Ajay Bhatt"
            },
            "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1_y" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Ray Tomlinson"
            },
            "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1_z" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Paul Buchheit"
            },
            "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1a-" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Ray Bradbury"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1_y",
          "order" : 4,
          "question" : "Who is credited with sending the first email?"
        },
        "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1a0" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1a1" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "A full-service digital agency"
            },
            "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1a2" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "A platinum Salesforce partner"
            },
            "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1a3" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "A cross-cloud Salesforce implementation specialist"
            },
            "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1a4" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "All of the above"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqjcYwDPDk3mIQq1a4",
          "order" : 5,
          "question" : "What is DEG?"
        }
      },
      "showGameOver" : false,
      "showGameResults" : false,
      "showQuestionResults" : false,
      "startTime" : 1527889800000
    },
    "-LDqkjkaEtSZ6CvpXEEk" : {
      "activeQuestionId" : false,
      "event" : "-LCUbqaXAuNRGFOJBXEL",
      "name" : "06/08/18 Game 1",
      "questions" : {
        "-LDqkjkYCO4Sd6CfpNZC" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqkjkZE5saP5OxlFuH" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Clothes"
            },
            "-LDqkjkZE5saP5OxlFuI" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "CDs"
            },
            "-LDqkjkZE5saP5OxlFuJ" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Books"
            },
            "-LDqkjkZE5saP5OxlFuK" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Safari vacations"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqkjkZE5saP5OxlFuJ",
          "order" : 0,
          "question" : "What was the first type of product sold on Amazon?"
        },
        "-LDqkjkZE5saP5OxlFuL" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqkjkZE5saP5OxlFuM" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "England"
            },
            "-LDqkjkZE5saP5OxlFuN" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "France"
            },
            "-LDqkjkZE5saP5OxlFuO" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Brazil"
            },
            "-LDqkjkaEtSZ6CvpXEEQ" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Russia"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqkjkZE5saP5OxlFuM",
          "order" : 1,
          "question" : "The 2018 World Cup is taking place in what country?"
        },
        "-LDqkjkaEtSZ6CvpXEER" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqkjkaEtSZ6CvpXEES" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "4.2 billion"
            },
            "-LDqkjkaEtSZ6CvpXEET" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "1.8 billion"
            },
            "-LDqkjkaEtSZ6CvpXEEU" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "6.1 billion"
            },
            "-LDqkjkaEtSZ6CvpXEEV" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "7.5 billion"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqkjkaEtSZ6CvpXEES",
          "order" : 2,
          "question" : "Out of the 7.6 billion people in the world, how many are Internet users?"
        },
        "-LDqkjkaEtSZ6CvpXEEW" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqkjkaEtSZ6CvpXEEX" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Wired"
            },
            "-LDqkjkaEtSZ6CvpXEEY" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "The Internet Movie Database"
            },
            "-LDqkjkaEtSZ6CvpXEEZ" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "MTV"
            },
            "-LDqkjkaEtSZ6CvpXEE_" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "America Online"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqkjkaEtSZ6CvpXEEX",
          "order" : 3,
          "question" : "Which company created the first web banner ad?"
        },
        "-LDqkjkaEtSZ6CvpXEEa" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqkjkaEtSZ6CvpXEEb" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "The Bible"
            },
            "-LDqkjkaEtSZ6CvpXEEc" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Guinness Book of World Records"
            },
            "-LDqkjkaEtSZ6CvpXEEd" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "A Tale of Two Cities"
            },
            "-LDqkjkaEtSZ6CvpXEEe" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Twilight"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqkjkaEtSZ6CvpXEEc",
          "order" : 4,
          "question" : "Which book holds the record of being the most stolen book from public libraries?"
        },
        "-LDqkjkaEtSZ6CvpXEEf" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqkjkaEtSZ6CvpXEEg" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "0"
            },
            "-LDqkjkaEtSZ6CvpXEEh" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "3"
            },
            "-LDqkjkaEtSZ6CvpXEEi" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "1"
            },
            "-LDqkjkaEtSZ6CvpXEEj" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "2"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqkjkaEtSZ6CvpXEEh",
          "order" : 5,
          "question" : "DEG is the only Salesforce partner to be named Marketing Cloud Partner of the Year how many times?"
        }
      },
      "showGameOver" : false,
      "showGameResults" : false,
      "showQuestionResults" : false,
      "startTime" : 1528493400000
    },
    "-LDqnMbKKeZxU_ulHyPc" : {
      "activeQuestionId" : false,
      "event" : "-LCUbqaXAuNRGFOJBXEL",
      "name" : "06/08/18 Game 2",
      "questions" : {
        "-LDqnMbIpVGZwN4TGisl" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqnMbIpVGZwN4TGism" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Louvre"
            },
            "-LDqnMbIpVGZwN4TGisn" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Van Gough"
            },
            "-LDqnMbIpVGZwN4TGiso" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Rijksmuseum"
            },
            "-LDqnMbIpVGZwN4TGisp" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "British Museum"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqnMbIpVGZwN4TGism",
          "order" : 0,
          "question" : "What is the most visited museum in Europe?"
        },
        "-LDqnMbIpVGZwN4TGisq" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqnMbIpVGZwN4TGisr" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "96 years"
            },
            "-LDqnMbIpVGZwN4TGiss" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "48 years"
            },
            "-LDqnMbJD6IY2O8yUvza" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "108 years"
            },
            "-LDqnMbJD6IY2O8yUvzb" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "59 years"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqnMbJD6IY2O8yUvza",
          "order" : 1,
          "question" : "Before winning the World Series in 2016, how many years did the Chicago Cubs go between winning a title?"
        },
        "-LDqnMbJD6IY2O8yUvzc" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqnMbJD6IY2O8yUvzd" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Moby Dick"
            },
            "-LDqnMbJD6IY2O8yUvze" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "The Old Man and the Sea"
            },
            "-LDqnMbJD6IY2O8yUvzf" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Typee"
            },
            "-LDqnMbJD6IY2O8yUvzg" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "20,000 Leagues Under the Sea"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqnMbJD6IY2O8yUvzd",
          "order" : 2,
          "question" : "The name Starbucks was inspired by the first mate in what Herman Melville novel?"
        },
        "-LDqnMbJD6IY2O8yUvzh" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqnMbJD6IY2O8yUvzi" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "The X-Files"
            },
            "-LDqnMbJD6IY2O8yUvzj" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Saturday Night Live"
            },
            "-LDqnMbJD6IY2O8yUvzk" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Mystery Science Theater 3000"
            },
            "-LDqnMbJD6IY2O8yUvzl" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Monty Python"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqnMbJD6IY2O8yUvzl",
          "order" : 3,
          "question" : "The term 'spam' was first used to refer to junk messages on what TV show?"
        },
        "-LDqnMbJD6IY2O8yUvzm" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqnMbJD6IY2O8yUvzn" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Charles Darwin"
            },
            "-LDqnMbJD6IY2O8yUvzo" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Oliver Cromwell"
            },
            "-LDqnMbKKeZxU_ulHyPW" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Winston Churchill"
            },
            "-LDqnMbKKeZxU_ulHyPX" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Sir Isaac Newton"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqnMbKKeZxU_ulHyPW",
          "order" : 4,
          "question" : "The late Diana, Princess of Wales, was distantly related to which prominent historical figure?"
        },
        "-LDqnMbKKeZxU_ulHyPY" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqnMbKKeZxU_ulHyPZ" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Kansas City"
            },
            "-LDqnMbKKeZxU_ulHyP_" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Denver"
            },
            "-LDqnMbKKeZxU_ulHyPa" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "San Francisco"
            },
            "-LDqnMbKKeZxU_ulHyPb" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "New York"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqnMbKKeZxU_ulHyPZ",
          "order" : 5,
          "question" : "Where is DEG headquartered?"
        }
      },
      "showGameOver" : false,
      "showGameResults" : false,
      "showQuestionResults" : false,
      "startTime" : 1528494000000
    },
    "-LDqxAKR82FLwX4sB_PE" : {
      "activeQuestionId" : false,
      "event" : "-LCUbqaXAuNRGFOJBXEL",
      "name" : "06/08/18 Game 3",
      "questions" : {
        "-LDqxAKQ-xghH0TEnshA" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqxAKQ-xghH0TEnshB" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "&"
            },
            "-LDqxAKQ-xghH0TEnshC" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "@"
            },
            "-LDqxAKQ-xghH0TEnshD" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "%"
            },
            "-LDqxAKQ-xghH0TEnshE" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "#"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqxAKQ-xghH0TEnshC",
          "order" : 0,
          "question" : "What symbol is used in an email address to indicate where the message is intended to go?"
        },
        "-LDqxAKQ-xghH0TEnshF" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqxAKQ-xghH0TEnshG" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "6"
            },
            "-LDqxAKQ-xghH0TEnshH" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "5"
            },
            "-LDqxAKQ-xghH0TEnshI" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "7"
            },
            "-LDqxAKQ-xghH0TEnshJ" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "4"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqxAKQ-xghH0TEnshI",
          "order" : 1,
          "question" : "How many red stripes are on the United States flag?"
        },
        "-LDqxAKQ-xghH0TEnshK" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqxAKQ-xghH0TEnshL" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "WebCrawl"
            },
            "-LDqxAKQ-xghH0TEnshM" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Backrub"
            },
            "-LDqxAKQ-xghH0TEnshN" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Handshake"
            },
            "-LDqxAKQ-xghH0TEnshO" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Hopscotch"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqxAKQ-xghH0TEnshM",
          "order" : 2,
          "question" : "What was the original name of the search engine now known as Google?"
        },
        "-LDqxAKQ-xghH0TEnshP" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqxAKQ-xghH0TEnshQ" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Oprah"
            },
            "-LDqxAKR82FLwX4sB_P1" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Martha Stewart"
            },
            "-LDqxAKR82FLwX4sB_P2" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Guy Fieri"
            },
            "-LDqxAKR82FLwX4sB_P3" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Ina Garten"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqxAKR82FLwX4sB_P1",
          "order" : 3,
          "question" : "In 2016, Snoop Dogg co-starred alongside which lifestyle guru on their collaborative cooking show 'Potluck Dinner Party'?"
        },
        "-LDqxAKR82FLwX4sB_P4" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqxAKR82FLwX4sB_P5" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Marketing Cloud"
            },
            "-LDqxAKR82FLwX4sB_P6" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Commerce Cloud"
            },
            "-LDqxAKR82FLwX4sB_P7" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Service Cloud"
            },
            "-LDqxAKR82FLwX4sB_P8" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Journey Cloud"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqxAKR82FLwX4sB_P8",
          "order" : 4,
          "question" : "Which of these is not one of Salesforce's Clouds?"
        },
        "-LDqxAKR82FLwX4sB_P9" : {
          "choices" : {
            "-LDqxAKR82FLwX4sB_PA" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Customers"
            },
            "-LDqxAKR82FLwX4sB_PB" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Environments"
            },
            "-LDqxAKR82FLwX4sB_PC" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Moments"
            },
            "-LDqxAKR82FLwX4sB_PD" : {
              "chosenCount" : 0,
              "text" : "Brands"
            }
          },
          "correctChoice" : "-LDqxAKR82FLwX4sB_PC",
          "order" : 5,
          "question" : "In DEG's tagline, the agency proclaims that it markets to what?"
        }
      },
      "showGameOver" : false,
      "showGameResults" : false,
      "showQuestionResults" : false,
      "startTime" : 1528494600000
    }
  },
  "players" : {
    "0s3r7yEj7gRzNoFaW2wGfzwWyub2" : {
      "active" : true,
      "email" : "ascheuler@degdigital.com",
      "event" : "-LCUWuNIqOKlRmpPvZTE",
      "firstName" : "Anna",
      "lastName" : "Scheuler"
    },
    "5biIuUJKBDV6dOVvRzSoXpDyEaN2" : {
      "active" : true,
      "email" : "ascheuler@degdigital.com",
      "event" : "-LCUWuNIqOKlRmpPvZTE",
      "firstName" : "Anna",
      "lastName" : "Scheuler"
    },
    "5j6igMzdffTqGY3BuunaKPWVVQN2" : {
      "active" : true,
      "email" : "rheap@degdigital.com",
      "event" : "-LCUWuNIqOKlRmpPvZTE",
      "firstName" : "Ryan",
      "lastName" : "Heap"
    },
    "HrnFh8lr76UEBtR2d32cBXBqFx33" : {
      "active" : true,
      "email" : "aladage@degdigital.com",
      "event" : "-LCUWuNIqOKlRmpPvZTE",
      "firstName" : "Aaron",
      "lastName" : "Ladage"
    },
    "aK6xWtxovRTz0gaAjIlFgn6dhgo1" : {
      "active" : true,
      "email" : "rheap@degdigital.com",
      "event" : "-LCUWuNIqOKlRmpPvZTE",
      "firstName" : "Ryan",
      "lastName" : "Heap"
    },
    "cjDL28OF3AN4qnyq6p4yZt2HOpB3" : {
      "active" : true,
      "email" : "aladage@degdigital.com",
      "event" : "-LCUWuNIqOKlRmpPvZTE",
      "firstName" : "Aaron",
      "lastName" : "Ladage"
    },
    "h1eWfB0CfTTcr7XKnqyav8ceHgq2" : {
      "active" : true,
      "email" : "ascheuler@degdigital.com",
      "event" : "-LCUWuNIqOKlRmpPvZTE",
      "firstName" : "Anna",
      "lastName" : "Scheuler"
    },
    "lNcu9GkIvuZmoo31l9gdoFjvRAj2" : {
      "active" : true,
      "email" : "rheap@degdigital.com",
      "event" : "-LCUWuNIqOKlRmpPvZTE",
      "firstName" : "Ryan",
      "lastName" : "Heap"
    },
    "sAysvz3egIMLFpQAQlulRsP1eW72" : {
      "active" : true,
      "email" : "aladage@degdigital.com",
      "event" : "-LCUWuNIqOKlRmpPvZTE",
      "firstName" : "Aaron",
      "lastName" : "Ladage"
    }
  },
  "questionDuration" : 15000,
  "resetApp" : false
}
